Axel INGOUF

axel.ingouf@gmail.com (438) 506-8557 www.axel-ingouf.com

Driver's license

ABOUT ME

I'm a game programmer passionate about AI, gameplay and engine programming with a past experience of full-stack web programmer. I'm fluent both in C/C++ and Java, but also have some good knowledge of C#, python and web languages. Along with Unreal Engine 4, I've already used Unity to make games, but also OpenGL, DirectX10 and more recently Vulkan. See my portfolio: www.axel-ingouf.com

EXPERIENCE

October 2018 – July 2019 | Quality and Security Full-Stack Developer at Boulanger S.A. Internship while studying at IMT Lille Douai.

April 2018 – June 2018 | International Internship at the NITSC University of Sendai, Japan Validation Internship while studying at IUT de Calais.

EDUCATION

2020 – 2021 | ISART Digital Montréal AEC Game Programming.

2018 – 2019 | IMT Lille Douai First year of Engineering School.

2016 – 2018 | IUT de Calais French "DUT" Computer Science Diploma.

SCHOOL PROJECT

January 2021 - June 2021 | 3D Game Engine using Vulkan in C++.

Final Project at Isart Digital Montréal.

SKILLS

Software Programming (JAVA, C, C++, .NET, C#, Python)

Game Programming (Unreal, Unity, Vulkan, OpenGL)

Web Programming (HTML/CSS, JavaScript, PHP, JQuery)

Versionning (Git, Perforce et SVN)

Network

Databases (MySQL, PostgreSQL)

Project Management (AGILE, Scrum)

Fluent in English with a TOEIC score of 975.

INTERESTS

New technologies Artificial Intelligences Fantasy and futuristic literature Video Games